http://www.iahd.org/en/privacy-policy-en

Privacy policy
The International Association for Handicapped Divers (IAHD) respects the privacy of all visitors to the IAHD web site and takes the utmost care to ensure that any personal information that you provide to the IAHD will be kept confidential. By using this site, you accept the terms of this policy. Any changes to this policy will be published on the IAHD web site.
The IAHD will only use the personal information that you provide, to help make your use of the IAHD site and the processing of any orders that you place, as easy and efficient as possible. Any other use will be made solely after obtaining your express permission. The IAHD will not sell your personal information to a third party and will only pass your personal information to a third party if this is necessary for the processing or delivery of your order.
International Association for Handicapped Divers (IAHD) uses the data provided by members and customers for the following services:
When you place an order, we require your name, email address, delivery address and payment details in order to process the order and to keep you informed as to the status of the order.
In order to ensure that shopping at the International Association for Handicapped Divers (IAHD) is as easy and efficient as possible, with your permission, we store details relating to orders and the use of our services. This enables us to personalise the web site to the specific preference of you and make suggestions that are relevant to you.
With your permission, we use your details to inform you of relevant developments on the web site and special offers and promotions. You can have this facility turned off by sending an email to the This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
If you create a personal account with the International Association for Handicapped Divers (IAHD), all details will be stored in a secure section of the web site. The details that are stored in a personal account with the International Association for Handicapped Divers (IAHD) include your name, email address, delivery address and payment details, so that this data does not need to be re-entered on a repeat visit to the web site.
Details pertaining to the use of our web site and the feedback that we obtain from our visitors help us to further develop and improve the web site.
International Association for Handicapped Divers (IAHD) will not sell your personal information.The IAHD will not sell your personal information to a third party and will only pass your personal information to a third party if this is necessary for the processing or delivery of your order. Our employees and partners are required to respect the confidentiality of your personal details.
Your personal details are safe with the International Association for Handicapped Divers (IAHD).Because we respect the trust that you have placed in us, we will exercise extreme care with processing and storing your personal details. When you place an order or access your International Association for Handicapped Divers (IAHD) account, be assured that you will be using the latest technology, such as “the Secure Socket Layer”, to ensure optimal security. For technical and operational reasons, it can be necessary to move your data to servers operated by partners of the International Association for Handicapped Divers (IAHD). Your personal details shall however, remain protected and confidential at all times.
Data breach.If you suspect that there is a data breach, then we ask that you to report this as soon as possible via our This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Should you have any questions regarding the International Association for Handicapped Divers (IAHD) privacy policy, please send an email to the This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. Our employees will be happy to assist you if you require further information or need help to change your details or settings.
Any changes to our privacy policy will be reflected in the most recent copy of this document on our web site.
With over 25 years' experience in recreational diving you've come to the right place for the complete diving experience.Anyone can learn scuba diving with us. Young or old, able-bodied or with physical or mental disabilities, you are welcome.
Privacy policy
Cookie policy
Disclaimer
Site map
Log in
© 1993 IAHD
Site developed and structure maintenance by maindes
Data maintenance by IAHD
